<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AbbaPark</string>

    <string name="learn_more">more</string>

    <string name="category_book">Book</string>

    <string name="category_thePark">The Park</string>

    <string name="category_home">Home</string>

    <string name="category_Activities">Activities</string>

    <string name="title">Title of card</string>
    <string name="description">Description of card</string>
    <string name="image">Imagen of card</string>


    <string name="home_one">Welcome to Mexico, and welcome to Abba Park. The nature reserve occupies 24 acres of the lush, stunning land of the Sierra del Tigre Mountains. You\'ll be surrounded by mountains, greenery, trees, rivers, and wildlife.  </string>

    <string name="home_two">6 Constitucion Street, Centro,  Concepcion de Buenos Aires, Mexico, ZP 49170 </string>

    <string name="home_three">Our fully functioning farm is tended to by traditional practices passed down for generations. Drink fresh milk, pick your eggs for breakfast, and allow the kids and yourselves to play alongside the cows, goats, chickens, and horses that spend their lives at Abba Park. </string>

    <string name="home_four">Your cabin in the woods has large, sweeping ceilings, a wood fireplace, hot showers, and is lit with natural candlelight. Each brick was hand created, and that intentional foundation steeped in hundreds of years of tradition can be felt within the walls. There are 24 acres of land to explore.</string>

    <string name="title_home_one">WELCOME TO ABBA PARK</string>

    <string name="title_home_two">VISIT US</string>

    <string name="title_home_three">THE FARM</string>

    <string name="title_home_four">THE ADOBE</string>

    <string name="activities_one">We\'ll explore Mexican farming and cooking techniques that have been passed down for generations.
On the farm made Pajarete / Breakfast / Cheese Factory / Tortilla factory / Adobe Factory / 4 hr $25.00  </string>

    <string name="activities_two">Mountain Biking Circuit / Guide shows you around \n 2 hrs $10</string>

    <string name="activities_three">Dinner / Mariachi / Folkloric Dance / Cazuela (tequila drink. Vampiro). \n Minimum of 8 people. \n 3 HRS $100 USD</string>

    <string name="activities_four">A massage by our in-house masseur. Book Online. \n Spa Service - Massage 1 hr $45</string>

    <string name="title_activities_one">A DAY ON THE FARM</string>

    <string name="title_activities_two">MOUNTAIN BIKING</string>

    <string name="title_activities_three">A DAY OF SONG AND DANCE</string>

    <string name="title_activities_four">SPA</string>

    <string name="thePark_one">Try our authentic flag ( Tequila + Lemon + Sangrita ) Black Charro ! Original Vampire ! Learn how to prepare you own cazuela !</string>

    <string name="thePark_two">The chef Maurice Salgado challenges the most demanding palates around the world with his author fusion cuisine</string>

    <string name="thePark_three">Duration varies • 20 dls and up Our Ziplines circuit are just awesome ! </string>

    <string name="thePark_four">Fire place, full private bathroom one or two bed, bbq area, camping equipment available just in the heart of the amazing forest ! </string>

    <string name="title_thePark_one">Sky Bar</string>

    <string name="title_thePark_two">Restaurant</string>

    <string name="title_thePark_three">Zip lines</string>

    <string name="title_thePark_four">Cottages</string>

    <string name="book_one">
Your cabin in the woods has large, sweeping ceilings, a wood fireplace, hot showers, and is lit with natural candlelight. Each brick was hand created, and that intentional foundation steeped in hundreds of years of tradition can be felt within the walls.</string>

    <string name="book_two">
Your cabin in the woods has large, sweeping ceilings, a wood fireplace, hot showers, and is lit with natural candlelight. Each brick was hand created, and that intentional foundation steeped in hundreds of years of tradition can be felt within the walls.</string>

    <string name="book_three">
Your cabin with two floors in the woods has large, sweeping ceilings, a wood fireplace, hot showers, and is lit with natural candlelight. Each brick was hand created, and that intentional foundation steeped in hundreds of years of tradition can be felt within the walls.</string>

    <string name="book_four">
Your cabin in the woods has large, sweeping ceilings, a wood fireplace, two flors, two hot showers, and is lit with natural candlelight. Each brick was hand created, and that intentional foundation steeped in hundreds of years of tradition can be felt within the walls.</string>

    <string name="title_book_one">Standard Room</string>

    <string name="title_book_two">Family Room</string>

    <string name="title_book_three">Master Room</string>

    <string name="title_book_four">Master Room *</string>


</resources>
